So, how's my newest parfait?
It's sweet and cold, and it's delicious!
Ui-chan, you're always like that.
Ah!
The ice cream!
futari de mita haruka kanata no ryuusei
二人で見た遥か彼方の流星
The distant shooting star we saw.
haato no puromisu
ハートのプロミス
Believe in our promise. As much as you'd call it true love.
ai to ieru hodo shinjite
愛と言えるほど信じて
You stop, as if you'd do that...
Hoshizora e
Kakaru
Hashi
Doki Fansubs Presents
Hoshizora e
Kakaru
Hashi
kaze ni yureru kami osaeru you ni
風に揺れる髪　抑えるように
...to keep your hair from fluttering in the wind.
kimi wa tomadoi
君は戸惑い
I painted my cheeks red...
koi no hajimari to kidukanai de hoo wo akakushita
恋の始まりと気づかないで 頬を赤くした
...so I wouldn't notice that I had fallen in love.
ikusen no hikari ryoute de hora
幾千の光両手でほら
You have myriads of light rays in your hand.
hoshi wo sukutte
星をすくって
Come on and save that star.
hitori no yoru demo waraeru you ni
一人の夜でも　笑えるように
So you can smile even on a night when you're alone.
omoi de wo hanabi ni shite
想い出の花火にして
Turn them into fireworks of your memories.
kimi to boku no uta ni nare
君と僕の唄になれ
And let them become a song for us.
saa ten made todoke kono kimochi
さぁ天まで届けこの気持ち
Let the heavens know...
kokoro wo gyutto tsunagou
心をぎゅっト繋ごう
...about our love that connects us firmly.
yowakutatte iin da boku no te de
弱くたっていいんだ僕の手で
It's okay if you're weak.
sono yume wo hippatte iku
その夢をひっぱっていく
I'll grab your hand and realise your dream.
kakehashi ni na itai yo
架け橋になりたいよ
I want to become your only bridge.
kimi hitori no kirari niji ni naru deshou
君一人のキラリ虹になるでしょう
I'm sure we will be shining forever...
boku ni kimi wo eien ni
僕に君を永遠に
...brightly like a rainbow.
Episode 9
Wasps are Diurnal
Geez, that Daigo...
He called me all the way out there, and in the end,
it was to show me a "very rare porn magazine" he collected.
What's with that?
Huh?
Sakai-senpai?
Hoshino...
What's wrong?
Sitting there all alone...
Senpai!
Is it a fever-
Doesn't seem to be the case.
Then...
Why?
Huh?
I'm... hungry.
I guess even you eat like that when you're hungry, right Senpai?
Ah, I was just pointing it out. In fact, it's a good thing.
Do you like girls that eat a lot, after all?
Eh?
Ah, that's...
More importantly, what happened, Senpai?
Why were you in such a weak state?
I left my house.
Left your house?!
Leaving the house means there is conflict between the parents and the child,
and the child has no intention of going back home.
I know what it means!
I had an argument with my father, and I just ran out of the house.
Without my wallet or a change of clothes...
I didn't bring anything.
So what are you going to do now?
It's not possible, even if you look at me with those eyes!
As it stands, I'm already freeloading off Yorozuyo Inn, so...
I know.
Thanks for the bread.
I'll work something out by myself.
Ah.
Senpai!
I'm back...
Senpai.
This is Hoshino's room.
Although it's small, please bear with living here for a while.
Ah, the ceiling is a bit low, so please be care-
Onii-chan, you came back!
Y-Yeah, I'm back.
Nee-san said dinner's ready.
Ah, got it.
Aren't you coming?
I've got some business to take care of first.
Tell Nee-san that I'll be right there.
Okay.
Senpai, what about your dinner?
I just ate a lot, so I'm fine for today.
I see.
I'll go eat my dinner, so please wait here for a while.
Wet Wipes
Senpai, sorry to keep you wait-
Ah!
Kazuma-kun!
What's wrong?
You shouted so loudly.
Ah, it's nothing!
It's just... a wasp flew into my room!
Wasps are diurnal.
Normally, they wouldn't be awake now-
That's not important now!
Kazuma-kun, are you okay?
Ah, I-I'm fine!
It already flew out.
W-What in the world were you doing?
I was sweaty, so I wanted to clean up my body.
If so, you should have just told me!
I would have brought you a towel.
I'm dressed, so you can turn around.
Don't scare me like that.
If Nee-san finds out-
I forgot to put that on.
Paradise, paradise!
A bath after work sure is the best!
So, Senpai, please sleep here tonight.
What about you, Hoshino?
I'll sleep on the floor.
I can't allow that.
I'm the one who's imposing.
Therefore, I should be the one to sleep on the floor.
Even if you say so...
I can't let a girl sleep on the floor while I sleep in the futon.
Then let's do this.
If we do this, we can both sleep in the futon.
Uh, that's a little...
Don't worry, I sleep very peacefully.
Well, it's not that...
I definitely won't kick you.
Right...
Senpai, what's the reason for your argument with your father?
Ah, if you don't want to say it, I won't force you to.
I'm thinking of going to Tokyo University.
Eh?
My father is against that.
He thinks if I go to the city, I'll never come back.
I get dizzy if I just get a whiff of alcohol,
so making sake is impossible for me.
But I could help out with the marketing.
So I want to go to university and study business management and product development.
Then I want to let more people know about our sake,
in as many ways as possible.
Senpai, have you told your father about this?
I've told him many times.
The first time I told him I wanted to go to Tokyo University,
he got very angry.
The second time, both of my parents suddenly became very irritated.
And the one after that, my father got angry again.
The next time, a huge argument took place.
And the time after that, a customer came in just as I was about to talk about it.
And the next time-
Ah, it's fine, I understand.
In the end, you didn't get to say it.
I get the feeling that I will never be able to say it.
That can't be true.
If a chance comes, you should take it.
That's right.
Hoshino.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
It's fine!
We should help people who are in need-
No.
It's not that.
When we first met, you said my strap was cute.
But I misunderstood and got angry.
Ah...
Don't make fun of me.
I'd been planning to apologise to you for that for a long time.
I was worried, since I couldn't get to say it.
Senpai.
Although you didn't get to say it then,
you just did, didn't you?
So, Senpai, you will definitely be able to tell
your father what you've been unable to say.
Hoshino.
What is it?
Thank you.
Kazuma-kun!
It's time for you to wake up!
Just because it's summer vacation doesn't mean you sleep in!
Kazuma-kun, are you awake?
I'm going to open the door!
W-Wait a sec!
I understand the circumstances.
I'm not thrilled that you didn't come to talk to me about this from the start,
but if a cornered bird flies to the hunter for shelter,
the hunter will...
...the hunter will...
...be surprised?
Even the hunter will refrain from killing
the bird that has flown to him for shelter.
Yeah, that's it!
Anyway, with that in mind, as the landlady of Yorozuyo Inn, I can't ignore someone in need.
However,
those that don't work don't get to eat.
While you're staying here, I'll have you work as a waitress.
Is that fine?
It looks great on you.
Er, why me too?
Since Tsumugi and her family went for short holiday,
I'm in need of another person right now.
So, I'll leave things to the two of you.
Hoshizora e Kakaru Hashi
Welco-
Father.
Hina.
Seems like you really are working here as a waitress.
Next up is cleaning up the entranceway.
Nee-san is good when it comes to making people work.
No!
I don't want to!
I'm telling you to come back with me!
Hey! Stop that!
Who are you?
I should be asking you that.
Huh?!
Father, stop it.
"Father", that means...
Oh, you were that dude from the city...
I see.
You were influencing Hina.
That's not true.
Hoshino has nothing to do with this.
Shut up!
You have no say in this!
She has no say?
It's because you always tell her that, that
she can't get across what she wants to say.
Isn't that true?
Huh?
You got something to say to me?
Senpai's planning to help your family business.
That's why she's going to university.
What?
She wants more people to know about your hand-made sake.
To make that happen, she said she wants to study!
Is that true, Hina?
If that was so, why didn't you say anything?
You didn't give her a chance to say anything!
Shut up!
Back off!
You back off!
This kid...!
Just because you came from the city doesn't mean you can treat your elders that way!
Stop right there!
Sakai-san, could you curb your violent ways here in Yorozuyo Inn?
This kid was being a prick, so...
But I'm bringing my daughter back!
Kazuma-kun is a valuable customer under our care.
And so long as he continues to be viewed as such,
your daughter is also a customer of ours.
As for me, even if the heavens try to stop me,
I will not tolerate any actions that harass our customers!
Sakai
Sake
Store
Darling, I got a call from the landlady at Yorozuyo Inn.
"Your daughter will be under our care, so please do not worry," she said.
Are you listening? You should stop pretending to sleep.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
See?
I knew you were awake.
You idiot!
Even if I was sleeping, I would wake up 'coz of that!
I heard from the landlady why Hina wants to go to the city.
"She wants to help her father's business", apparently.
Seems like I gave birth to a good girl.
It's not just you that gave birth to that kid.
So, what are you going to do?
What do you mean, what am I gonna do?
She's our cute daughter, and it's not like I don't know why you want to keep her by your side.
But you've got to keep her feelings in mind.
I know that perfectly well.
I know that...
Yorozuyo Inn
Eh?
Senpai's father wants to have a battle with me?
Well, even though he says "battle", it's just a tug-of-war contest.
Huh?
Tug-of-war?
It's an old custom.
When two villages are in dispute, they
send out their strongest representatives,
and in front of Kotama Shrine, they
decide who wins by the tug-of-war contest.
During my grandmother's time, there were even things like two men who were both chasing the same girl,
and they decided who would get
her through the tug-of-war contest.
To think that there are still people who want to settle disputes through such a method...
But why does he want to challenge me?
It seems that he thinks Kazuma-kun is the
disgusting insect sticking to his dear daughter.
Disgusting insect...
So, what are you going to do?
Are you going to accept this challenge?
Hoshino, it's fine if you don't accept it.
I don't want to cause you any more trouble.
No, I will accept this.
I will make your stubborn father silently accept his defeat.
If Kazuma-kun is the winner, she gets to make her own choice.
If Sakai-san is the winner, she has to go home quietly. All right?
Yes.
Seems like you're ready.
Nee-san, do I really have to wear this?
Of course.
Since this is a customary shrine activity,
you've got to wear the traditional outfit.
And why are there so many people watching-
Onii-chan!
Ayumu, why are you wearing that?
Well, Nee-san said I had to wear this if I really wanted to cheer for Onii-chan.
Do you understand?
This is a fight for victory before the gods!
Make sure you fight and leave no regrets.
The younger kid has the nicer butt, doesn't he?
It's so smooth. I'm jealous!
I wonder if my kid could marry him?
Right?
Dear mothers!
It's a battle before the gods, so please cease your harassment!
So, competitors, please pick up the rope.
Start!
Onii-chan, you can do it!
Hoshino...
Come on, put your all into it, Sakai-do!
Don't lose to that kid!
It's gonna be hard to predict the outcome!
Father...
Senpai...
Please fulfil your dream!
The outcome is decided!
The contest is over!
Onii-chan!
Senpai?
Ah, this was just...
Darling, are you okay?
Well then...
Shall we start eating?
Father isn't here yet.
Leave him alone.
Father has been in a bad mood ever since the contest.
He's holed up in his room and doesn't want to come out.
Maybe he still hasn't forgiven me.
That isn't the reason.
He didn't want to compete seriously with that Hoshino kid,
and was planning to lose to him.
Eh?
To act as a father silently supporting his daughter, he wanted to throw the match,
but before he could do that, he went all out and ran out of stamina.
As I thought, in the end, it didn't go well.
He's sulking because of the bad result.
Hmm.
Maybe it's because of age.
In the old days he was fast, and he could have handled it easily.
Hold on, where are you going?
Father.
Are you sulking?
Father, you're cute.
Idiot! Don't make fun of-
The times when you're shy...
...are cute too.
Father.
Thank you.
chotto matte yo
ちょっと待ってよ
Wait a second!
yume no tsuzuki kana
夢の続きかな
Why are you continuing with your daydreams!
shigyou beru no gofun mae da (u—n)
始業ベルの五分前だ(うーん)
You were studying just five minutes ago
mezamashi mo nidone
目覚ましも二度寝
Your alarm clock already rang twice
ja shouganai ne
じゃ、しょうがないね
So it can't be helped
yada seifuku no manma nechattetanda demo rakkii
やだっ制服のまんま寝ちゃってたんだ... でもラッキー?
Oh no! I slept with my uniform on, but how lucky!
hai tenshon de ikou konna tokya!
ハイテンションでいこう こんな時ゃ!
It's time to go with high tension!
nandemo kandemo DORAMA ja arumaishi
何でもかんでもドラマじゃあるまいし
Everything isn't like in drama's
umakuiku monka tte omotteta (fu—n)
うまくいくもんかって思ってた(ふーん)
I thought it would turn out smoothly
shokupan wo kajiri
食パンをかじり
Nibbling on white bread
kado wo magaru
角を曲がる
Make the corner curve
to hatto! masaka ne
とハッと...! まさかね
See! It's impossible!
sukippu sukippu
スキップスキップ
Skip! Skip!
mousou darake de
妄想だらけで
Full of crazy ideas!
dasshu dasshu
ダッシュダッシュ
Dash! Dash!
chikoku wa genjitsu sokka sokka
遅刻は現実 そっかそっか
Being late has become reality, I see, I see
sekai wa kyou mo todokoori naku janjan mawaruyo
世界は今日も 滞りなくじゃんじゃんまわるよ
The world today is also filled with love, climbing non-stop
ii kanji de (hai)
いい感じで(ハイ)
It feels great
hashire hashire
はしれはしれ
Run! Run!
otome otome
オトメオトメ
Girl! Girl!
GO! or GO!
Go or Go
itsudatte
いつだって
As always,
kyou ga numbah one saikou tte sakende ikiteyaru
今日がNo.1 最高って叫んで生きてやる
Shout out, "Today is number one!" "Today's the best!"
hashire hashire
はしれはしれ
Run! Run!
otome otome
オトメオトメ
Girl! Girl!
GO! & GO!
Go & Go
tatoeba hito tobi taimumashin de
例えばひとッ飛びタイムマシーンで
For example, a one-leap time machine.
sore tte saikou (saiko desu—)
それって最高(さいこですー)
That's the greatest!
Ayumu-kun!
It's time for the preview!
Ah, he's asleep.
Well, it's fine.
I shall be the replacement.
Next time, on Hoshizora e Kakaru Hashi, episode 10:
The Ring, Flowing Down the Stream...
Next time
Dragonfly...
There's a dragonfly!
He said there's a dragonfly!
I wonder what dream he's having.
Now there's a Japanese Rat Snake!
Eh?!
A Japanese Rat Snake?
Ah!
The cobra...
Onii-chan's King Cobra is...!
Ayumu-kun! Run!